### AKANKSHA PANDYA CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working currently attending ICL Graduate Business School, with 5+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of customer communications, customer service, and order processing skills to successfully fill the Customer service representative role at any company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE**

Communication & Training services limited , Auckland Jun 2021 - Present

- Maintain working knowledge of quality standards.
- Develop and perform quality test processes.
- Tracking and examining call flow,
- Calling patterns, established quality assurance levels, and the rate of call abandonment.

#### STORE MANAGER

Silver lining of companies limited trading as Spice traders, Onehunga, Auckland, Auckland Jan 2016 - Feb 2021

- Inventory stock and reorder when inventory drops to a specified level.
- Instruct staff on how to handle difficult and complicated sales.
- Hire, train, and evaluate personnel in sales or marketing establishments, promoting or firing workers when appropriate.
- Assign employees to specific duties.
- Provide customer service by greeting and assisting customers, and responding to customer inquiries and complaints.

#### FIELD COORDINATOR

Center for Indian Bamboo Resources And Technology, Vyara, India, Vyara, Gujarat / Aug 2014 - Oct 2014

- Visit individuals in homes or attend group meetings to provide information on agency services, requirements, or procedures.
- Keep records or prepare reports for owner or management concerning visits with clients.

### REFERENCES

References available upon request

- akankshapandya90@gmail.co m
- **\** (022) 176-8161
- ₱ 7/19 Locarno avenue Sandrin gham Auckland , 1025

#### **EDUCATION**

## ICL GRADUATE BUSINESS SCHOOL

Auckland

Masters of Management (Expected graduation Oct 2022)

### UUNZ INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS

GPA: 59
Auckland

Post graduate certificate in business Business Administration (Dec 2015)

# SHREE J M PATEL INSTITUTE OF SOCIAL WORK

GPA: 81.2 Anand

Masters of social work (May 2013)

# ANAND INSTITUTE OF SOCIAL WORK GPA: 64.77

Anand

Bachelor of social work (Apr 2010)

### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Complex problem solver
Work ethic and time
management
Communication and teamwork
Service-focused
Employee Training